<?xml version="1.0"?>
<GalleryContents xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<GalleryUiContents>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Getting Started with Dynamo</Header>
		<Body>Dynamo is a visual scripting program that will help you compose custom algoritms to process data and generate geometry. With Dynamo, you can generate code without having to know how to code.&#10;&#10;Learn about the basics of Dynamo on the next few pages.</Body>
		<ImagePath>01-Welcome.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>The Building Blocks of Dynamo</Header>
		<Body>[1] Nodes represent objects or functions.&#10;[2] You can wire nodes together to form a set of instructions on how to process data and/or build geometry.&#10;[3] How nodes are wired together will determine the order of operations. Data flows between the nodes and is executed in the graph from left to right.  </Body>
		<ImagePath>02-BuildingBlock-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Node Anatomy: Input, Output, Previews</Header>
		<Body>[1] Input Port: Hover over it to reveal the default value and what type of input it accepts&#10;[2] Output Port: Hover over it to reveal the type of output the node returns&#10;[3] Preview Bubble: To get more details about a node’s output, hover over the node for 1 second to reveal its preview bubble. Preview bubbles can’t be typed into, and you can keep the preview bubble open by clicking on the pin icon.  </Body>
		<ImagePath>03-Anatomy-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Finding and Placing Nodes</Header>
		<Body>The Dynamo Library is located on left side of the screen.&#10;[1] Search: Use the Library Search to find nodes&#10;[2] Browse: Discover nodes in the Library Categories&#10;[3] Add Nodes: After you find a node in the library, just click on it or drag it over to the canvas to place it. </Body>
		<ImagePath>04-Place-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Wiring Nodes</Header>
		<Body>You can “wire” up nodes to build a set of instructions.&#10;[1] Click on the output port of one node, then [2] Connect it to the input port of another.&#10;[3]Wires appear dashed when they are not connected. Click on an empty spot in the canvas to delete a wire.&#10;[4]Deleting Wires: Click on one of its ports. Then, click on an empty spot in the canvas.</Body>
		<ImagePath>05-Wiring-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Graph View  vs. Background 3D Preview</Header>
		<Body>In Dynamo, you will see 2 views simultaneously: the Graph View and the Background 3d Preview.&#10;[1] Switch from graph view to the background 3d preview&#10;[2] Independently control the zoom of each view&#10;[3] Pan around each view</Body>
		<ImagePath>06-View-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Packages</Header>
		<Body>Can’t find a node that does what you want? Search user-generated collections of nodes, also known as pacakges, in the Package Manger. &#10;&#10;The Package Manger can be accessed from the top menu under "Packages".</Body>
		<ImagePath>07-Packages.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Tips and Tricks</Header>
		<Body>[1] Code Block Node: Double-click on the canvas to add a node that you can use to enter numbers, strings, and DesignScript, Dynamo’s scripting language.&#10;[2] Watch nodes: Add a watch node to add a permanent view of a node’s output&#10;[3] Range Syntax: Easily make a list of numbers or letters&#10;[4] In-canvas Search: Right-click over the canvas to quickly bring up a search bar</Body>
		<ImagePath>09-Tips-L.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	<GalleryContent>
		<Header>Need More Help?</Header>
		<Body>There are more resources to help you learn more about Dynamo.&#10;- dynamobim.com: Dynamo's official website&#10;- dynamoprimer.com: Dynamo's official Getting Started Guide&#10;- Sample Files: Check out examples in the top menu under "Help > Samples"</Body>
		<ImagePath>10-Help.png</ImagePath>
	</GalleryContent>
	</GalleryUiContents>
</GalleryContents>